ITEMS FOR SALE
ITENS À VENDA

ITEMS
ITENS

PROFITS
LUCROS

SOLD OUT
VENDIDO

COLLECT PROFIT
RECOLHER LUCRO

TAKE ITEM
PEGAR ARTIGO

Out of stock, come back another time!
Esgotado, volte outras vezes!

ADD ITEM
ADICIONAR ITEM

Select an item from your inventory to add
Selecione um item do seu inventário para adicionar

ACCEPT
ACEITAR

Set Price
Definir preço

To buy this, you need
Para comprar isso, você precisa

Buy XYZ for
Compre XYZ por

Buy ABC XYZ for
Compre ABC XYZ por 500